喂 过来这
Psst. In here!
终于安全了 先别放松啊
I'm safe. Not quite.
请把你的护身符交出来 斯丁森先生
The amulet, please, Mr. Stinson.
为什么
Why?
救命 救命 那个孩子
Help! Help! The kid.
救命 撑着点 孩子
Help! Hang on, kid.
赶紧抓着我的领带
Grab my tie.
可是你不应该把你的领带解下来啊
But you're not supposed to take the tie off.
你跟你的朋友莉莉和马修打赌输了
You lost a bet with your friends Lily and Marshall
所以你必须要戴着领带一整年
which requires you to wear the tie for a full year.
如果这可以救你一命 我相信他们会理解的
If it means saving your life, I think they'll understand!
他们听起来想是非常善良的人啊
They sound like nice people!
是的 他们的确是
Yeah, they are.
赶紧抓住
Grab that...
上来吧
Come on.
抓住了
That's it.
谢谢你 先生
Thanks, Mister.
我要怎么报答你呢
How can I repay you?
如果你非要坚持的话 好好学习 天天向上吧
You can stay in school, that's how.
不
No!
这就是事情的真相
True story.
但是 我会怀念
But golly, I'm just gonna miss
那条该死的鸭子领带  真的
the heck out of that ducky tie. I really am.
看看我刚从垃圾堆里发现了什么
Look what I just found in the trash.
不是吧
No!
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第九集
翻译： Henry   andie  47.4 MR.GAO
后期： 霜之哀伤  校对： Henry 园丁姐姐
HIMYM字幕组倾情奉献
孩子们 要是你没有让别人在你干过蠢事的地方
Kids, you haven't truly lived until somewhere,
立上一个警告牌的话 你就不算真正的活过
somebody puts a sign up because of something you did.
比如
For instance...
请问你们有看到门口的警告牌么
Have you guys seen that sign out front that says
绝对不允许趴板冲浪
"Absolutely No Boogie-Boarding"?
怎么回事呢
What's that all about?
噢 这是个好段子 你有时间听么
Oh, that's a great story. You got time for it?
唔 我现在应该是去参加我妈妈的生日派对 所以
Well, I'm supposed to go to my mom's birthday party, so...
请你把这个故事讲的越长越好
please make it as long as you can.
好吧 这个事情发生在几个月以前
Well, it happened a few months ago.
在一个飓风袭击的夜晚
The night of the hurricane...
孩子们 那是2011年8月26日
Kids, it was August 26, 2011,
飓风艾琳正在袭击整个纽约
and Hurricane Irene was barreling towards New York.
同志们 童鞋们 亲们
Guys, guys, guys.
飓风是一种非常严重的自然灾害
This storm is serious.
幸运的是 你们的朋友是一个前任童子军
Luckily, you are friends with a former Boy Scout.
而且童子军是做什么的
And a Boy Scout is always what?
不受欢迎的 被揍的
Unpopular? Beaten up?
被妈妈带着一起看电影的
Going to the movies with his mom?
一个童子军是随时做好准备的
A Boy Scout is always prepared.
准备在自己的储物柜里独自享用午餐
Prepared to spend lunch in his locker?
准备在保持处男之身而死
Prepared to die a virgin?
准备去帮自己的姐妹淘涂指甲
Prepared to paint his sister's nails?
是为所有的事防范于未然
Prepared for emergencies!
这就是为什么一个星期以前
That's why a week ago,
当飓风艾琳还是一个热带低气压
when Irene was just a tropical depression-
你就是个热带低气压
You're a tropical depression.
我给大家准备了
This guy got us...
一个应急背包
a disaster backpack,
还有租了一辆五个座位的汽车而且刚好停在楼下
and a rental car that seats five, parked right outside.
我们准备去我位于韦斯切斯特的家
We're gonna drive up to my place in Westchester
在那里可以保证我们的安全
where we'll all be safe.
你们刚刚被童子军拯救了 还有不用谢
Boy Scouted! You're welcome.
泰德是对的 我们应该离开这里
Ted's right, we should go.
嘿 在我们离开这个城市的时候
Hey, on the way out of the city,
你介意在我家停一下我去拿点东西么
do you mind if we stop at my place so I can get something?
可以啊 你准备拿些什么
Okay, what did you have to get?
我的酒啊 我们才不去任何地方
My drink on. We're not going anywhere.
什么 不可能
What? No!
我们没有时间来做这些了 我们需要赶紧走
We don't have time for this! We gotta get going!
泰德 我比你年长 是的
Ted, I'm older than you. Yeah.
比你魁梧 只有年龄老点
And taller. Just older.
当你到我这个岁数的时候 还有身高
And when you reach my age, and height,
你会感觉一些事情 比如说飓风根本不足一惧
you'll see that things like this hurricane are no big deal.
他们正准备关闭整个大桥
They're going to close the bridges.
大伙们 我们需要赶紧离开这
You guys, we got to get out of here.
我估计这次我要站在小金毛这边
I'm afraid I'm with blondie on this one.
这个飓风根本没什么 我可是来自温哥华的
This storm is nothing. I'm from Vancouver.
你知道在我们那都怎么称呼飓风的么
You know what we call this in the Couv?
可以烤烧烤的天气
Barbecue weather.
是啊 我也同意他们俩的观点
Yeah, I'm with these guys.
一边喝酒一边看巴尼的硕大的电视
Drinking beer in front of Barney's giant TV
完胜一晚上呆在车里
beats sitting in the car
听艺妓回忆录
listening to Memoires of a Geisha.
拜托 我们可以听最精彩的部分
Come on, we're at the best part.
噢 是我妈妈打来的 看看我现在是否安全
Oh, it's my mom, checking to see if I'm okay.
嘿 妈
Hey, Mom.
喔 妈咪 外面现在一团糟
Ooh, Mommy! It's dwizzling out!
我好怕怕
I'm so scared!
可以穿比基尼的天气
Bikini weather.
马修 你跟我站在统一战线上 对吧
Marshall, you're with me, right?
不好意思 老朋友
Sorry, old friend.
不过我禁不起命运的诱惑
But I can't afford to tempt fate.
噢 我记得了 我那时候我表现的非常奇怪
Oh right, I was being really weird.
我应该解释一下
I should explain.
去年夏天我辞掉了我的工作
Last summer I quit my job.
然后 在飓风到来的前一周
And then, a week before the hurricane...
噢 我的医疗保险过期了
Huh, my medical insurance just expired.
在我加入到你的保单计划前 刚好有两周的时间
That gives me two uninsured weeks before I'm added to your plan.
这没什么大不了的
It's no biggie.
噢喔 被纸划伤了
Ow! Paper cut.
我们已经被死亡的气息环绕着
Death is all around us.
所以接下来的两个星期
So for the next two weeks
他基本上表现的非常像埃德加・爱伦・坡
he was basically a really clingy Edgar Allan Poe.
死神的召唤
The Grim Reaper beckons.
我感觉到他冰冷的双手缠绕着我的喉咙
I feel his icy grip around my throat,
他的呼吸一直紧随着我的脚跟
the breath of his hounds at my heels,
他那紧凑的镰刀砰砰声敲打我的心房
the unrelenting rat-tat-tat of his scythe on my chamber door.
还有你 和你愉快的请求
And you, with your blithe request,
你只催促他取得死亡的胜利
you only hasten his inevitable triumph.
这就是你的欲望么
Is that what you desire?
这是得你的欲望么 莉莉
Is that what you desire, Lily?
我只是想让你帮忙买点百吉饼回来
I just wanted you to get us some bagels.
百吉饼
Bagels?!
你知道么
Do you have any idea
在我去买百吉饼的路上会发生什么么
what could happen to me whilst getting bagels?!
我擦 不要这样啊
What the...?! No, not like this!
那好 我去买百吉饼
Fine. I'll go get the bagels.
不行
No!
为什么不行
Why not?
还有记住 不要太多奶油芝士
And remember, not too much cream cheese.
涂一半 足量
Half a shmear, max.
谢谢啦 宝贝
Thanks, baby.
啊 不要啊 不要这样
No! No! Not like this!
你知道么 你现在就是非常荒谬啊
Okay, now you're just being ridiculous.
是得 生活有时候就是这么荒谬 莉莉
Well, life is ridiculous, Lily!
人们有时候会被公车碾过
People get run over by buses
还有被滑板破蛋 被婴儿咬伤
and hit in the nuts by skateboards, bitten by babies.
没有人一睁开眼就说 今天会在优酷里
Nobody wakes up and says, "Today I'm gonna star
成为明星
in a YouTube video."
你说那句话不下十遍了
You've said that at least a dozen times.
莉莉 在接下来的两个星期
Lily, for the next two weeks
你必须跟我在一起而且保护我
you must be by my side protecting me.
为什么 什么事情会发生
Why, what's gonna happen?
飓风来袭
a hurricane.
拜托让我摘下这个领带吧
Just let me take off the tie! Please!
我不得不戴着它工作
I have to wear this at work.
你真的理解么 这是有多么的痛苦
Do you have any idea what that's like?
如果SEC公司起诉成功的话 这会让我们很头疼的
If the SEC pursues charges, it's going to be all our asses.
没有人像我一样严肃的对待这件事
Nobody takes this more seriously than I do.
拜托啦 我可以摘下来么
Please, can I take it off?
你可以 戴
You... may... knot.
不能摘哟 亲
With a "K."
一个小小的领带双关语
A little tie pun.
我跟你没完
This is far from over.
你一定有个妥协的价码 艾瑞克森 而且我找到的
You have a price, Eriksen, and I will find it.
今夜结束后 我就会摘下这个领带
When the end of day is nigh, I'll have taken off this tie.
我将会爱死了我那时候的装扮 我保证
I'm going to like the way I look, I guarantee it.
趴板冲浪到底是嘛回事
So boogie-boarding...
趴板冲浪嘛 当时我正努力地让大家离开
Boogie-boarding. So I was trying to get these guys to leave.
嘿 讨厌鬼
Hey, Nerdlinger,
不都说最安全的蠢蛋么
what's with the safety boner?
我是说 看看你
I mean, come on.
应急装备 车子 还有女式雨靴……
The disaster kit, the car, the ladies' rain boots-
啊 这是男式的
Uh, they're men's.
粉色容易被救援者识别
Pink is just easier to spot from the rescue chopper.
听着 原谅我太关心你们了
Look, forgive me for caring about you guys,
但你们是我在这个世界上最好的朋友
but you're my best friends in the world
我只想确保你们平安无事
and I just want to make sure you're okay.
啊 泰德 你就是个十足的扫兴鬼
Ah. Ted, you are a giant whining bummer.
巴尼
Barney...
放松点 泰德
Come on, Ted,
暴风雨没什么大不了的
this storm is not a big deal.
暴风雨很猛烈
This storm is a big deal.
我们再来看看艾琳飓风
Let's replay that harrowing footage
侵袭北卡罗莱纳的悲惨画面
of Irene touching down in North Carolina.
我们必须离开这里
We gotta get out of here!
走吧 走吧 快点 快点
Go, go! Come on, come on!
-请让我把它摘了吧 -没门
-Please let me take it off!
-No.
-五千块 -别想
-$5,000?
-No.
他没开玩笑吧
Is he serious?
一万块
$10,000?
-不行  -伙计们 答应他吧
-No.
-Dudes, take the money.
-两万块  -不可能
-$20,000?  -No.
-同意 -我让你使劲扇我耳光
-Yes. -I'll let you slap me in the face as hard as you can.
我有点兴趣了
You have my attention.
孩子们 你们还记得马修和巴尼的耳光赌约吧
Kids, you remember Marshall and Barney's slap bet.
几年以前 巴尼打赌输给了马修
A few years earlier, Barney lost a bet to Marshall.
他的惩罚是在任意时间 任意地点被扇五个耳光
His penalty was five slaps delivered anyplace, anytime.
目前为止 马修已经扇了巴尼四个耳光
So far, Marshall had slapped Barney four times.
这意味着他只剩一个耳光了
Which meant he only had one slap left.
你觉得怎么样 马修
What do you say, Marshall?
你要不要抓住这次“击会”
Are you going to seize this slap-ortunity
还是直接放过它
or let it slap through your fingers?
别让他诱惑你 马修
Don't let him tempt you, Marshall.
我不知道 莉莉 我是说 我们就要有宝宝了
I don't know, Lily. I mean we have a baby on the way.
新的扇耳光机会又这么唾手可得
An extra slap could really come in handy.
不 不
No! No!
这太疯狂了
This is crazy.
那条领带你再戴十个月
You having to wear that tie for another ten months
我已经够满足的了
is all the satisfaction I need.
再说
Plus,
我还可以扇一个耳光
I still have one slap left,
-这样感觉很好 -但如果你不留着那个耳光
-and that feels good. -But if you didn't have that slap left-
比如说 我会让你今晚就扇
if say, I were to get you to slap me tonight-
我觉得一切都会改变
I suppose that would change everything.
我也觉得会
I suppose it would.
游戏开始了
Le jeu commence.
我是玩家马修
Je m'appelle Marshall.
说说趴板冲浪   回到趴板冲浪
So boogie-boarding... Boogie-boarding.
我试图让这些人离开
So I was trying to get these guys to leave,
但遇到个小问题
but there was one little problem.
来吧 一起走
Come on, let's go.
我留下
I'm staying.
什么 巴尼
What?! Barney?!
嘿 嘿 外面会变得很疯狂
Hey, hey, it's going to get pretty crazy out there.
如果哪个辣妞的衣服都被吹跑了
And if some hot woman gets all her clothes blown off,
而我没有呆在这里把它录下来
and I'm not up here to videotape it
然后传到网上 还能指望谁会这么做呢 联邦应急管理局吗
and put it up on the Internet, who will, FEMA?
好了 醒醒吧
Come on, open your eyes.
不 你和我们一起走
No, no, you are coming with us.
不抛弃不放弃呢 亲
We leave no man behind.
嘿 妈妈
Hey, Mom.
啊 是的 靴子很抢眼
Uh, yeah, the boots were a big hit.
我最好上个厕所
You know, I better pee.
等莉莉和我回来 我们就走
But when Lily and I get back, we're all leaving.
什么 我要和你一起上厕所
Wait, I have to go pee with you?
你想让我一个人去“厕所”
You want me to go to the "Bathroom,"
这个世界上最危险的地方
the most dangerous room in the house by myself?
你知道会发生什么吗
Do you have any idea what could happen?
哦 我的眼睛
Ow! My eye!
我看不见了
I'm blind!
不 不 别这样
No, no! Not like this!
我觉得关于即将发生的事
I don't think we're seeing eye to eye
我们都要持不同意见了
about the likelihood of that happening.
嘿 是我爸
Hey, it's my dad.
我爸给我打电话了
My dad's calling me.
嘿 你知道泰德从哪里  得来的靴子
Hey, do you know where...? Ted got his boots?
是的 帅呆了 我也很想要一双
Yeah. They're fabulous. I totally want a pair.
好的 爸爸 我会的 谢谢
Okay, Dad, I will. Thanks.
伙计们 老爸说这场暴风雨比想象的严重的多
Guys, Dad says this hurricane is a bigger deal than you thought.
我来负责 我们得离开这儿了
I'm taking charge. We are getting out of here.
好吧 怎么每个人的父母都打电话来
Okay, what is with everybody's parents calling
问候他们
to check up on them?
不过是点小雨罢了
It's just a little rain.
这天气都可以修草坪呢
Lawn-mowing weather.
还可以玩室外地滚球
Bocce weather.
哇 你真是被打击到了
Wow. You're really bummed
你老爸不担心你
that your dad's not worried about you.
什么
What?!
呃 我爸有什么好担心的
Eh... What would my dad be worried about?
我没抹够防晒霜吗
That I'm not wearing enough sunblock?
仅仅是能粉刷房子的天气吧
House-painting weather.
泰德 你回来了
Ted, you're back.
我改变主意了 我跟你们一起 走吧
I've changed my mind. I'm in. Let's go.
是的 我也改变主意了 你不能来
Yeah, I changed my mind, too. You can't come.
其他人 我们一起出去
Everybody else, we're moving out.
太伤人了
That's harsh.
你知道还有什么伤人吗 紫外线
You know what else is harsh? Ultraviolet light.
这礼拜我在晒黑床上睡着了
I fell asleep in the tanning bed this week
我想我的脸被晒伤了
and I think I got a sunburn on my cheek.
它好敏感
It's so sensitive.
看起来就像大大红红的公牛眼
It's like a big, red bull's-eye.
疼疼哟
Ouchie.
你是不是把腮红从我包里拿走了
Did you take my blush out of my purse?
说说趴板冲浪
So, boogie-boarding.
对 趴板冲浪
Boogie-boarding.
哦 算了 泰德
Oh, come on, Ted,
你不能就这样把他留下
you can't just leave him here.
啊 是的 我可以
Uh, yeah, I can.
你说我是一个十足的扫兴鬼
You called me a giant whining bummer.
你不能上我的车
You're not allowed in my car.
你不会知道艺妓有没有遇见真爱
You don't get to find out if the geisha finds love.
这是原则问题
This is about principle.
嘿 泰德 我准备好了
Hey, Ted. I'm ready to go.
你就是传说中的原则吧
And you must be "Principle."
啊 插播一下 伙计们 这是玛雅
Ah, on a separate note, guys, this is Maya.
我刚在大厅外面认识她
I just met her out in the hall.
我们有很多共同点
We have a lot in common,
比如说都爱乡村音乐
such as our mutual love of country music,
全美汽车比赛协会还有杰夫・福克斯伍斯（乡村音乐家） 别深究
NASCAR and Jeff Foxworthy. Just go with it.
她需要搭便车出城
She needed a ride out of the city,
我们又有一个空位 所以
and we have an extra seat in the car, so...
好 我们出发
Okay, let's hit it!
哇噢
Wow.
事情发展成这样
It's come to this.
你本可以帮助一个朋友
You could help a friend,
但你却选择了一个穿紧身背心
but instead, you're choosing the hot girl in
的辣妹
the tight tank top.
你出师了
Your training is complete!
我真为这孩子骄傲
I'm so proud of this kid!
言归正传 暴风雨就要来了
But seriously, the storm's coming in,
甩了这个小妞 走起
so dump the hoochie and wheels up.
你答应给我留个位置的
You promised me a seat.
哦 看在上帝的份上
Oh, for God's sake.
你们都去 我留下
You two both go. I'll stay here.
-什么 莉莉 不    -我坐副驾
-What? Lily, no!  -Shotgun!
你留下 那莉莉就和我们一起 什……
You're staying. Then Lily can come! Wha...?
-不不不 我就留在这儿     -为什么
-No, no, no, I'll stay here.    -Why?
我只想离开你一会儿
I just want some time away from you!
什么
What?
马修 对不起 我爱你
Marshall, I'm sorry. I love you,
但这两个星期里 我没有单独待过一秒
but I haven't had a second alone in weeks!
这可是暑假啊
It's summer vacation!
我只想坐在浴缸里读书
All I want to do is sit in the bathtub
但现在……
and read a book, but now...
宝贝 我忘记带书了
Baby, I forgot to bring a book.
你介意把书给我读出来吗
Do you mind reading yours out loud?
嘿 我也觉得不爽好吧
Hey, it's been no picnic for me either.
你甚至不模仿角色的语调
You don't even do the voices.
没来电显示
Blocked number.
你好
Hello?
小罗宾吗 我是你爸
RJ? It's your father.
爹地
Daddy?
我爱你
I love you.
你打电话来对我真的很重要
It means so much that you called.
哈 我就知道你在等他的电话 小样
Ha! I knew that you wanted him to call. Busted!
那是你吗
That was you?
我真的认为你该扇他
I really think you should slap him.
你该狠狠的扇他
You should slap him!
扇他 扇他
Slap him. Slap him.
两边的脸都等着你哦
Two cheeks, no waiting.
好啊 我确实感觉该扇他
Good, 'cause I really think I'm gonna slap him!
那么 趴板冲浪
So, boog -boarding?
嗯
Boogie-boarding.
别这样啊 泰德
Come on, Ted.
你宁愿随便带上个妓女
You're gonna give some random floozy a ride,
也不愿意捎带上巴尼么
but not take Barney?
妓女
Floozy?!
如果她走我就不走
If she's going, I'm not going!
-莉莉 你留下   -我们走
Lily, you're staying.   -Let's go.
如果莉莉留下 我也要陪她
If Lily's staying, then I'm staying!
-那我就要走   -那我也走
-Then I'm going.   -Then I'm going.
你不能走 马修 因为我要走
You can't go, Marshall, 'cause I'm going.
-如果巴尼要走 我就不走   -那我就可以走了
-If Barney's going, I'm not going!   -Then I can go.
-那我留下   -那我也留下
-Then I'm staying.   -Then I'm staying.
那我走
Then I'm going.
那我就不走了
Then I'm not going.
好吧 你知道么 我决定走
Okay, you know what? I'm going.
这阵风暴在多普勒天气雷达上出现了一个礼拜了
This storm's been on Doppler radar for a week.
而我却是唯一为之做了准备的人
I'm the only one who prepared for it.
而你们却一直取笑我 你们猜猜我会干啥
And you all made fun of me. So guess what?
我这个童子军要走了 拜拜了您们啦
This Boy Scout is taking a hike. Good-bye!
玛雅 快速回答一下 你感觉我们俩有可能么
Maya, real quick, did you think there was anything here, or...
哦 我有男朋友了
Oh, I have a boyfriend.
再见
Good-bye!
额 泰德
Um, Ted...?
疏散的时间已经结束了
The time for evacuation is over.
大家应该呆在室内
Everyone should now go inside and be prepared
直到最早礼拜天下午
to stay inside until weather conditions improve,
天气情况转好为止
which won't likely be until Sunday afternoon.
我们被困在这里了么
We're stuck here?
好吧  别紧张
Okay, let's not panic.
我们还是紧张吧
You know what? Let's panic.
嘿 如果我们撑不过今晚
Hey, if we don't make it through the night,
我希望你们能知道 我想严肃的说
I want you guys to know, and I really mean this...
我希望我能在20岁那年过得更放浪 结交更多的朋友
I wish I had branched out and made more friends in my 20s.
好吧
Well,
我要去厕所了
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
我猜 就我一个人了吧
By myself, I guess.
小心有熊
Watch out for bears.
既然今晚可能会是最后的一晚了 我得坦白一些东西
Since this might be the end, I gotta confess something.
可以么
Can I?
请便
Might as well.
在过去的一段时间里
Barney and I have been doing the wild thing...
除掉去年巴尼和马修的妈妈鬼混的一小段时间
this whole time.
我和巴尼
Except a brief period last year when he was shacking up
经常滚床单
with Marshall's mom.
幸运的是 3P已经提上了日程 所以
But luckily, three-ways were on the menu, so...
马修 你知道她没说那些 是吧
Marshall, you know she didn't say any of that, right?
是的 但我就是想狠狠的抽他
I know, but I just want to slap him so bad!
但这个领带看上去蠢透了 但我还是很想扇他
But that tie is so stupid! But the slap would feel so good!
但他恨透了这条领带
But he hates that tie so much!
或许我可以帮上一些忙
Perhaps I can help.
马修 问问自己这个问题 为什么是今天
Marshall, ask yourself this question: why today?
他整整憋了几个星期没去抱怨这条领带
He hasn't said anything about that tie for weeks,
一直到 今天
and yet, suddenly today,
他就不能再戴着这条领带多一秒么
he can't wear it another second?
不 因为这其中必然有隐情
No, there's a reason.
你一定隐藏了一些什么
You've got something coming up.
一些你不想说出来
Something where you're
显得自己处于弱势
on display, vulnerable...
并暴露自己的事情
exposed.
这跟工作无关
It's not work-related.
哦 这一定是跟情感挂钩的
No, this is relationship stuff.
你一定是想让某些人对你印象深刻
You're trying to impress someone.
在你开篇撒的那个谎中
In the lie you told,
你说你被两个傻子追着
you said you were being chased by two goons.
所以是两个人
So it's two people.
可能是一对情侣
A couple, perhaps.
你明天要去见诺拉的父母
You're meeting Nora's parents tomorrow!
不对
Wrong!
错 错 错 错 错
Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong!
是两天后 我真的希望他们能够喜欢我
It's in two days, and I really want them to like me!
哦 理疗师般的推理
Oh-ho! Therapisted!
该说心理医师的推理
Shrinked? Shrunk?
我回头会弄清楚的
We'll figure it out.
那么 趴板冲浪
So, boogie-boarding.
嗯 趴板冲浪
Boogie-boarding.
嘿 莉莉 我能和你说几句话么
Hey, Lily, can I talk to you for just a second?
来
Come here.
马修 如果你让我来帮你刷牙 我发誓...
Marshall, if I'm in here to brush your teeth, I swear to...
很抱歉 最近我这么黏人
I'm sorry that I've been so needy lately.
我知道 你需要一些独处的时间
I know that you need some time alone.
那么 我去别的房间了
So... I'll be in the other room.
你哪儿也不用去
You're not going anywhere.
嗯 嘿
Mmm... Hey...
有趣的是
And the funny thing is,
自从那晚上之后 我们永远都不会一个人了
after that night, we'll never be alone again.
你们在我的浴室里尽情的翻滚了
You made that in my bathroom?
哇哦
Whoops.
哇 一个飓风孩子
Wow, a hurricane baby.
哇哦 伙计 艾瑞克森 飓风 可是个好名字
Oh, man, Hurricane Eriksen would be a sweet name.
这是个爆好的名字啊
It would be a crazy sweet name!
谢谢了您呐  泰德
Thanks, Ted.
不管怎么说 第二天危险过去了
Anyway, the next day, after the danger had passed...
关门了
It's closed.
现在怎么说
Now what?
童子军总是有所准备的
A Boy Scout is always prepared.
嘿
Hey!
好样的
Nice!
为我们在飓风中幸存下来 干杯
To surviving the hurricane.
耶
Yay!
-我爱你们   -我也爱你
-I love you guys.   -Love you.
那周晚些时候我才回到了公寓
I did finally make it up here to the house later that week
发现一颗倒了的橡树
only to find that a falling oak tree had
压在了客厅里
landed in the living room.
如果我们在那儿的话 会被像虫子一样被压死的
If we'd been here, it would have crushed us like bugs.
看到没有 孩子们 永远没有办法知道
You see, kids, there's no way of knowing for sure
哪儿才是最安全的地方
where the safest place is...
所以最好的期望就是 找到一些好伙伴
so the best you can hope for is to have some good company.
伙计们 你们猜我用这个当滑板冲浪能冲多远
Guys, how far do you think I can boogie-board on this thing?
心有多远你就能冲多远
So far!
马修 你的医保要到明天才能生效
Marshall, your insurance doesn't kick in till tomorrow.
无所谓
Yeah, well, you know what?
享受生活从这一刻就生效了
Life kicks in right now.
别担心 他没伤着
Don't worry, he wasn't hurt...
当然 那是第一次冲得时候 我有急救夹板
the first time. I have splints!
第二次嘛 他直接穿过了酒吧的窗户
The second time he went through the front window of Maclaren's.
就是现在放着 严禁爬版冲浪标志的地方
Hence the "No Boogie-boarding" Sign.
好的 伙计们 我要走了
All right, guys, I gotta go.
巴尼 祝你见诺拉父母时好运
Barney, good luck with Nora's parents.
-拜   -拜
Bye.   -Bye.
再见
See you later.
-好的 再见   -再见
-All right. See you.   -See ya.
嘿 巴尼
Hey, Barney?
嗯
Hmm?
听着 我们在你的浴室
Listen, um, we made a baby
造出了宝宝
in your bathroom.
所以我们欠你个人情
So we owe you one.
所以我们认为
So we say...
你可以拿掉那个鸭子领带
you can take off the ducky tie.
代价是再被我扇三巴掌
For three slaps.
三巴掌
Three slaps?
事先澄清一下 是追加三巴掌
And to be clear, this would add three slaps
加上之前剩下的一个 一共是四巴掌
to Marshall's existing one, giving him four slaps in total.
成交
Deal.
我自由了
I'm free!
天啊 这感觉太好了
God, this feels so good!
不 这是个错误
This was a mistake!
我想戴回领带
I wanna put the tie back on!
给我那条领带
为什么我要在现在变回原来的巴尼
Why do I have to be Barney right now?
还剩三个耳光
Three slaps remaining!
三个耳光 哇哦 我喜欢这声音
Three slaps. Wow, I like the sound of that.
我觉得我可以挽救这些坏蛋
I think I'll save those bad boys,
你懂得 以备不时之需
you know, for a rainy day.
好吧 最坏的已经过去了
Okay. The worst is over.
啊
Ah!
还剩两个耳光
Two slaps remaining!
我还好
It's all right.
嘿 已经结束了
Hey, it's all done...
只是现在哟
for now.
我觉得我要回家了
I think I need to go home
去重新评估我该如何做各种人生决定
and reevaluate how I make life decisions.
来吧 我要回去工作了
Come on. I have to go back to work.
我们拼车吧 好吧 恩
Let's split a cab. Okay. Yeah.
你告诉过那些家伙另外一件
Did you ever tell those guys about that other thing
差点发生的事吗
that almost happened?
另外一件事
That other thing?
哦 那个啊 没 呢
Oh, that. No. Did you?
没
No.
关于那个电话我很抱歉
Hey, I'm really sorry about that phone call.
哦 还好
Oh, it's fine.
不 那不好 我就是个混蛋
No, it is so not fine. I was a jerk.
如果你不在意的我的说法 你爸爸没打电话
And if you don't mind my saying, your dad is
他就是一个十足的蠢蛋
a complete idiot for not calling.
他应该每天都给你打电话的
He should never let a day go by without calling you
因为我要是有一天没有跟你说话
because when I let a day go by without talking to you...
额 那一天就过的不好
Um, that day's just no good.
额 不好意思
Um, sorry.
额
Um...
那是我爸爸
It's my dad.
等一下 让我看看你的手
Wait, show me your hands.
啥都没有
My hands.
嘿 爸爸
Hey, Dad!
那就是我一直都在说的
That's what I've been saying!
高尔夫天气
Golf weather!
你能相信我们差点就
Can you believe we almost...?
我知道
I know.
我们没做的好事
Good thing we didn't.
恩 我是说 那不久之后
Yeah. I mean, not long after that
你跟诺拉在一起了
you got together with Nora.
你也遇见了凯文
And you met Kevin.
恩 灾难避免了
Yeah. Disaster averted.
确实是
Exactly.
如果我们这么做了会毁掉一切的
It would've ruined everything if we'd been all...
啊 啦啦啦
ah-la-la-la...
我知道 对的 那太白痴了
I know, right? So dumb...
啦啦啦啦啦
La-la-la-la-la-la...
（whoa 欢呼的BR党们）